//@flow

import {CardType} from "./types.js";

const cardData: CardType[] = [
    {
        front: "commencer; 1st person singular",
        back: "je commence",
    },
    {
        front: "commencer; 2nd person singular",
        back: "tu commences",
    },
    {
        front: "commencer; 3rd person singular",
        back: "il commence",
    },
    {
        front: "commencer; 1st person plural",
        back: "nous commençons",
    },
    {
        front: "commencer; 2nd person plural",
        back: "vous commencez",
    },
    {
        front: "commencer; 3rd person plural",
        back: "ils commencent",
    },
    {
        front: "manger; 1st person singular",
        back: "je mange",
    },
    {
        front: "manger; 2nd person singular",
        back: "tu manges",
    },
    {
        front: "manger; 3rd person singular",
        back: "il mange",
    },
    {
        front: "manger; 1st person plural",
        back: "nous mangeons",
    },
    {
        front: "manger; 2nd person plural",
        back: "vous mangez",
    },
    {
        front: "manger; 3rd person plural",
        back: "ils mangent",
    },
    {
        front: "jeter; 1st person singular",
        back: "je jette",
    },
    {
        front: "jeter; 2nd person singular",
        back: "tu jettes",
    },
    {
        front: "jeter; 3rd person singular",
        back: "il jette",
    },
    {
        front: "jeter; 1st person plural",
        back: "nous jetons",
    },
    {
        front: "jeter; 2nd person plural",
        back: "vous jetez",
    },
    {
        front: "jeter; 3rd person plural",
        back: "ils jettent",
    },
    {
        front: "acheter; 1st person singular",
        back: "j'achète",
    },
    {
        front: "acheter; 2nd person singular",
        back: "tu achètes",
    },
    {
        front: "acheter; 3rd person singular",
        back: "il achète",
    },
    {
        front: "acheter; 1st person plural",
        back: "nous achetons",
    },
    {
        front: "acheter; 2nd person plural",
        back: "vous achetez",
    },
    {
        front: "acheter; 3rd person plural",
        back: "ils achètent",
    },
    {
        front: "espérer; 1st person singular",
        back: "j'espère",
    },
    {
        front: "espérer; 2nd person singular",
        back: "tu espères",
    },
    {
        front: "espérer; 3rd person singular",
        back: "il espère",
    },
    {
        front: "espérer; 1st person plural",
        back: "nous espérons",
    },
    {
        front: "espérer; 2nd person plural",
        back: "vous espérez",
    },
    {
        front: "espérer; 3rd person plural",
        back: "ils espèrent",
    },
    {
        front: "essayer; 1st person singular",
        back: "j'essaie",
    },
    {
        front: "essayer; 2nd person singular",
        back: "tu essaies",
    },
    {
        front: "essayer; 3rd person singular",
        back: "il essaie",
    },
    {
        front: "essayer; 1st person plural",
        back: "nous essayons",
    },
    {
        front: "essayer; 2nd person plural",
        back: "vous essayez",
    },
    {
        front: "essayer; 3rd person plural",
        back: "ils essaient",
    },
];

export default cardData;
